iso.org 2011-06-06

# ISO - Privacy Policy

  * 

Thank you for visiting ISO Online. The International Organization for Standardization is committed to protecting the privacy of its members, customers, and other contacts. Any information you choose to provide on the Web site will only be used to provide or improve the services we offer.

###  Acceptance 

By browsing this Web site, communicating electronically with us and/or submitting your personal data to this Web site, you acknowledge and agree to to the terms of this Privacy Policy and to the processing of personal data by ISO as described below.

###  Personal information 

We will collect personal information about you only with your consent - for example, when you:

  * use our Web store for purchasing International Standards or related publications,
  * subscribe to our magazines, ISO Focus, or ISO Management Systems,
  * request specific information or products,
  * subscribe to the IMS Alerts e-newsletter.

Personally identifying information that you provide by e-mails or Web forms will be used only for such purposes as are described at the point of collection, such as to send information or products to you, to update your membership record, or to respond to your questions or comments.

We will use such personally identifiable data only for business purposes within the International Organization for Standardization, which includes communication with ISO member bodies. We do not share personally identifiable data collected at this site with third parties except in the following cases:

  * We may transfer your personal data to our partner agencies (service providers) which assist us in administering ISO Online. These partner agencies are bound by a contractual agreement to keep your data private and secure.
  * We may disclose personal data if we are required to do so by law or if such action is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process, to respond to any claims, or to protect the rights of ISO, its customers and the public.

From time to time, we may ask our site visitors to answer survey questions. Surveys generally deal with the site, our products or categories of products and they will not request any personally identifiable data.

###  Information collected and stored automatically 

As you browse through ISO Online, we will automatically gather and store information about your visit via cookies. This information does not identify you personally. The data collected may include information on the pages you visited and how often you visited them. We use cookies only to assist us in measuring traffic on our Web site and to enable us to improve the quality of service we offer you via ISO Online.

###  Links to Other Sites 

ISO Online contains links to other sites. If you access other sites using the links provided, the operators of those sites may collect information from you which will be used by them in accordance with their own privacy policies. ISO is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. We encourage you to become familiar with the privacy policies of any other sites which you visit, including sites linked from ISO Online.

###  Revisions 

ISO reserves the right to change or modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we revise our privacy policy, we will post the changes on the site to ensure transparency of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

###  Accessing, Deleting or Correcting Data 

You can consult, revise and correct the personal data that you have provided to the ISO Web store via [www.iso.org/myaccount](https://store.iso.org/isoweb/app?page=account%2FLoginMain&service=external&sp=Sen "My account").

If you are receiving the IMS Alerts e-newsletter you can unsubscribe at [www.iso.org/IMSAlerts/unsubscribe.](http://www.iso.org/iso/imsalert_form_leave.html "http://www.iso.org/iso/imsalert_form_leave.html")

Alternatively, you can send an e-mail to the ISO Online [Webmaster.](mailto:webmaster@iso.org "Webmaster")

###  Referrals 

Some ISO Web areas may provide you with the opportunity to e-mail a Web page to another person. For this feature to work, we may need to collect your e-mail address and/or the e-mail addresses of those to whom you send the Web page. The e-mail addresses collected in this context are not used for any purpose other than to send your request. Under applicable laws, they are deleted as soon as your request is fulfilled.

###  Governing Law 

This Privacy Policy is governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of Switzerland. You agree to submit any dispute arising out of your use of this Web site to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of Switzerland.
